YOU TREATMENTS FOR CANCER,
SOMETIMES IT KILLS YOUR
BLOOD CELLS AND YOU
NEED TO REPLENISH WITH
FRESH BLOOD. EVERY YEAR,
400 ,000 KIDS WORLDWIDE
GET CANCER. NOT 400
,000 PEOPLE, 400 ,000
KIDS GET CANCER,
NO CHILD SHOULD DIE
OF CANCER. WE DESPERATELY
NEED BLOOD, YOU'RE A
HERO. YOUR DAD DONATED
BLOOD, NOW YOU GOTTA
BE NICE TO HIM
THE NEXT WEEK, YOU'RE
HERE AND YOU'RE SAVING
LIVES. ONLY TWO AND
A THREE PERCENT OF
ELIGIBLE ADULTS ACTUALLY DONATE
BLOOD, THANKFULLY YOU BROUGHT
OUT ALL THESE AMAZING
PEOPLE TODAY TO DONATE.
AND IT'S BECAUSE OF
THEM, WE'VE RECEIVED ENOUGH
BLOOD TO SAVE 8
,000 LIVES. OBVIOUSLY, YOU
CAN DONATE MONEY,
DONATING BLOOD IS AN
AMAZING THING. THAT'S A
CRAZY LIFE. IF YOU
CAN'T DONATE MONEY,
YOU CAN DONATE BLOOD.
LIKE THAT. GAVE SOMEONE
LIFE QUITE LITERALLY.
IT FEELS AMAZING.
EVERY YEAR, MORE THAN
105 ,000 KIDS AROUND
THE WORLD LOSE THEIR
LIVES TO CANCER.
BUT BEHIND EVERY LIFE
THAT IS SAVED IS
AN ARMY OF DOCTORS,
RESEARCHERS,
VOLUNTEERS AND ORGANIZATIONS LIKE
ST. BALDRICKS, WHERE HEROES
AND VOLUNTEERS SHAPE THEIR
HEADS IN SOLIDARITY WITH
KIDS FIGHTING CANCER. WHEN
I WAS GOING THROUGH
LEUKEMIA, MADE ME FEEL
GREAT.
AND COMPANIES LIKE AMGEN,
WHO ARE DEVELOPING THE
NEXT GENERATION OF CANCER
TREATMENT. NO CHILD SHOULD
DIE OF CANCER. BASIC
RESEARCH GIVES ME INCREDIBLE
HOPE, SO THE CHILDREN
DON'T HAVE TO GO
TWO AND A HALF
YEARS OF TOXIC THERAPY.
AND LIKE, STAND UP
TO CANCER, WHO ARE
WORKING EVERY DAY TO
CHANGE THAT.
AND TOGETHER,
EVERY STEP BRINGS US
A LITTLE CLOSER TO
A WORLD WITHOUT CANCER.
I WAS DIAGNOSED AT
21 YEARS OLD WITH
THE HELP OF RESEARCH
AND INNOVATION.
I WAS ABLE TO
GET OTHER TREATMENT OPPORTUNITIES.
FIVE YEARS CANCER -FREE,
SO WE'RE GOOD. YEAH,
LOVE IT. IN THIS
VIDEO, YOU SAW THIS
GRANT 100 KIDS WISHES.
I THINK ALL OF
US WOULD AGREE. THE
ULTIMATE WISH FOR THEM
WOULD BE TO NOT
HAVE TO DEAL WITH
CANCER IN THE FIRST
PLACE, WHICH IS WHAT
STAND UP TO CANCER
IS DOING BY FORMING
A DREAM TEAM AND
RAISING MONEY. TO GET
THE TOP PEOPLE ON
THE PLANET WHEN IT
COMES TO CANCER RESEARCH,
TO TRY TO PUT
AN END TO PEDIATRIC
KIDS' CANCER, AND WHY,
I WANT TO SUPPORT
THAT MISSION. SO BOYS,
BRING IT ON IN.
ME AND MY FRIENDS
AT AMGYN AND ST.
PAUL DREX ARE GOING
BE MAKING A $6
.5 MILLION DONATION TO
HELP KICKSTART THE DREAM
TEAM.
THIS $6 .5 MILLION
IS GOING TO CHANGE
A LOT OF KIDS'
LIVES. LIKE THE LINCOLN
ASSCRIPTION,
GOING TO NEED MORE
THAN $6 MILLION TO
SOLVE THIS ISSUE. NO
KIDS SHOULD HAVE TO
DEAL WITH CANCER AND
HOPEFULLY THIS HELPS STOP
IT.
TAKE CARE.